字幕翻譯：william2568
Subtitled by: william2568
- william2568 出品 -
你知道我是從哪得到創立3X項目這一靈感的麼？
You know how I came up with the idea of Triple-X program?
用兩個詞概括就是：滑板和游泳池
Skateboards and swimming pools.
奧古斯都·吉本斯 極限特(3X)項目創始人
Augustus Gibbons Founder of the XXX Program
一己之力阻止第三次世界大戰
Single-handedly Stopped World War 3
1977年的時候 滑板十分流行 那時滑板一般是放在地面上玩的
Skateboards used to be stuck on the ground, unless in transportation.
只有運輸時才會把它們放在交通工具裏
In 1977 habits.
突然一場罕見的旱災襲擊了南加州
A big drought hit southern California.
災情嚴重 水量不足 向游泳池中灌水的費用十分高昂 連富裕的城市居民都支付不起相關費用
Got so bad that rich urbanites could not afford to fill their swimming pools.
有個孩子靈機一動 他轉念一想
That's when the light clicked on. Some kid figured it out ...
不用在意這些空游泳池 到外面去多走走好了
He could escape these empty pools and get some real nasty air
狗鎮和滑板少年 這部電影你看過麼
Dogtown and Z-Boys. Have you seen it? It is a movie.
沒看過？無所謂了
Does not matter.
這個孩子開始用"滑板"玩出各種新鮮又極限的招式
Anyhow, our hero starts doing things on a board ...
從來沒人想到過滑板還能這麼玩
and no one had ever seen.
大家覺得這簡直不可思議
Things the world thought were impossible.
總結一下 要是沒有那場旱災
Now that kid needed it, that draught.
就沒有這些空的游泳池 那個孩子估計也想不出那些好點子
The world needed those empty pools.
我也正是從他的點子裏 得到了創立極限特工項目的靈感
That's why Triple-X.
小內馬爾 計劃將其招入極限特工項目 足球天才
NEYMAR JR. XXX Active RECRUIT OF A GENIUS WITH BALL at his feet
20歲時進球數已達100球
Scored 100 goals by age 20
以為吉本斯要把他招進復仇者聯盟中
THOUGHT he was being recruting for THE AVENGERS
你覺得你今天比昨天更安全麼？我反正不這麼覺得
Do you feel safer today than you felt yesterday? I know I do not.
美國的軍隊 世界規模第一 裝備總價最高
The biggest, most expensive military in the world ...
但機場裏那些小炸彈還是把美國人民嚇得雞飛狗跳
and we are still scared the shoes and tiny whitey bombs at the airport.
為什麼會這樣？
Why is that?
因為那些士兵只會服從軍令 在戰場上衝鋒陷陣
Beacuse the soldiers are built to take orders and fight in wars.
但我們這些普通老百姓 雖說沒有在戰場上廝殺
But we, my friend, are not at war.
但也是危機四伏
We are at peril.
3X項目的意義就在於此
That's why Triple-X.
你咋不吃飯？在減肥？你不餓麼？
What's matter? You are on a diet? You're not hungry?
現在才早上7點30分呢
It's 7:30 in the morning.
那又如何？世界上別的地方還在吃中飯或者晚飯呢？快吃啊！
So? It's lunch or dinner time somewhere in the world. Come up! Eat up!
你知道在這個世界裏 哪種人覺得安全麼？那些掌權的 以及他們的副手
You know who does feel safe? The man in charge. The world beaters.
還有那些中東富得流油的宗教領袖 只有這幾種人才會覺得安全
The top chief par excellence ayatollahs with all the dollars.
那是因為 這些道貌岸然的混蛋
And that's because those righteous bastard somewhere along the way ...
跟魔鬼做了筆交易 他們犧牲自由 保證了自己的人身安全
made a deal with the devil. They traded liberty for safety. And us ...
至於我們這些普通老百姓
we the people
沒錢沒自由 人身安全也得不到保障 這時候極限特工就要站出來了
ended up losing both. That's why Triple-X.
大家思維受局限的時候
While anybody else is stuck on the ground ...
我們就要拿出讓人耳目一新的東西 玩出新花樣
we're doing shit on the board nobody's even seen before
我的故事講完了
Well, that's my pitch
我一直覺得我不太擅長這些說辭
I've always worked as spy better than a salesman
聽完這些 你怎麼看？
So, what do you say?
我當不了英雄 我就是個踢足球的罷了
I'm not a hero. I'm just a footballer.
抱歉浪費了你的時間
My bad.
那我直接走人好了
So I leave you be there.
我走人 你買單 誰說天下沒有免費的早餐 這不就是麼
Who says that there is no such thing as free, meal
所有人趴在地上！快！把錢都給我！
Down on the ground! Now! Give me the money!
被動！
Do not move!
動作快點！
Hurry up!
射門！
Goal!
你剛剛才說你當不了英雄呢
And you say you're no hero.
我覺得你就是扯淡
I gotta call bullshit on that!
你就是那種項目需要的 能夠拯救世界的英雄
You're exactly the kind of hero the world needs.
最後 我要問你一個老掉牙的問題了
At the end of the day, it comes down to the same question ...
我每週五晚都會問我妻子這個問題 已經堅持20年了
I've been asking my wife every Friday night for the last 20 years.
你想不想來體驗一下這種生活呢？
Do you want some of this?
還是你...
Or you just gonna...?
極限特工：終極回歸
Return of the Xander Cage
紐約 中情局總部
CIA HEADQUARTERS NEW YORK CITY
允許進入
access granted
好的 各位可以坐下了
Okay you may sit.
先生們
Gentlemen...
這就是那個讓衛星墜毀的裝置 吉本斯因公殉職
This is the device that crashed the satellite and killed Gibbons.
實驗室的書獃子們給它起了個綽號 "潘多拉魔盒"
Nerds in the lab had coined it "Pandora's Box".
我的小隊追蹤了衛星最後發回的信號 信號點位於邁阿密
My team backtracked satellite's last signal input to Miami.
某個住在麗思·卡爾頓頂級豪華酒店的混蛋
Some assholes leading the high life at the Ritz-Carlton pentahouse...
以為他能借此向全世界好好勒索一筆
thought he could hold the world ransom.
特工們突襲了他的住處 過程就不敘述了 當場擊斃
Three flashbangs, two bullets and one body back later ...
我們得到了這個設備
we took custody of the device.
為了防止某些瘋子黑客劫持我們的衛星
We must have over hundreds redundancies in place...
我們可是有數百項防範措施呢
to prevent some punk with a laptop from hijacking satellites.
對於"潘多拉魔盒"來說 這都不是事
And Pandora's Box can bypass them all of them.
只需按下一個按鈕 它就能監聽加密的衛星通訊
With of a push a button, it can eavesdrop on secured communications ...
破壞軍用軟體 傳遞虛假情報
corrupt military software, transmit false intelligence or ...
還能把衛星當戰術導彈使呢 想打哪就打哪
crash a satellite out of the sky like a goddamn tactical warhead.
坐在這個房間裏的某個人就是幕後主使
One of you is behind this.
要麼你現在給我站出來 要麼今天我們都別走
I am not leaving until I find out who.
你用一本書跟我鬥？
You fight me with a book?
來打我啊 兄弟 把書翻到第一章！
Here you go, brother! Chapter 1!
第一頁！
Page One!
最煩這些書獃子了
Sheer habits.
你遲到了
You were late!
老闆 我這不是來的正好麼
Just in time, boss.
他們從天而降 踩著我們的臉
They busted in here, step on our throats ...
搶走了那個能導致世界政局劇變的裝置
and take the one device that can cause a global power shift.
那我們怎麼才能把它弄回來？
So how do we get it back
那些混蛋眨眼間就幹掉了我們的菁英 猶如探囊取物
These assholes just took our best of the best like they were in a Sunday brunch.
我們得找一個像他們一樣身手敏捷的人
We need someone who move like them, fight like them.
他可以走進一場龍捲風
We need someone who can walk into a tornado ...
再從裏面毫髮無損的走出來 彷彿那只是習習微風般
and come out the other side like it was a damn gentle breeze.
你認識這樣的人麼？
Do you know someone like that?
不
No.
但是吉本斯給我們指了一條明路啊
But Gibbons did.
挑戰1 倒計時
DEFCON 1
快下來！你在幹什麼！
Get down from there! What are you doing?
桑德！
Xander!
謝謝你 先生
Gracias, senor.
好了 比賽開始了！
And here we go! We are on the way!
桑德 我就知道你能辦到 你把我們的世界都點亮了
I knew you would do it, Xander. You brought the world to us.
世界很大 但你的心也很大呀
The world is big, but always fits in your heart.
你還有很多東西可以學
Take it with you always
去看電視吧
Now, go, go.
其實你可以像普通人一樣
Of course Xander Cage could pay the satellite company ...
支付衛星電視的費用吧
just like a regular guy
咋了？
What?
你的意思是我應該乖乖掏錢給那些公司老闆們？
And line the pockets of some boardroom billionaires?
我跟你說
You know
這年頭 想當個付得起錢的普通人 可不容易喲
These days, a regular guy can't afford to be a regular.
- 爬上來 - 走吧
- Up. - Let's go.
滑板規則1 別摔跤
Rule 1 Don't fall.
多米尼加 聖多明各
Santo Domingo. Dominican Republic.
是不是感覺世界越來越小了
Is the world getting smaller?
我能理解你的感受
I know the feeling.
一味逃避是解決不了問題的
Running from your problems never works out.
你需要換個思路了
You need a new plan.
我只需要份新的地圖
I need a new map.
可別說我沒提醒過你喲
Do not say I did not warn you.
我的天
Oh boy.
又是這一套
Here we go again.
別動 你這個混蛋
Get down. Do not move asshole
跪在地上！
On your knees now, you son of bitch!
我是真的想按你的話照做 但你說的話我真的不明白
I want to comply, I really want to comply but you're confusing me.
一方面你叫我"別動" 另一方面你叫我"跪下" 那我到底該咋辦？
"Do not move, asshole". "On your knees you son of bitch" Which is it?
- 給你三秒鐘 跪下！ - 你演技真的不行
- You have three seconds to comply! - You're not good at this.
一！
One!
二！
Two
好了
Okay!
怪人 出來吧！
Come out, Frankesnstein!
吉本斯！快出來！
Gibbons! Gibbons?
我在這呢
Olly, olly, oxen free.
吉本斯 你確實大變樣了啊
You really do look different, Gibbons.
你是不是減肥了？
Did you lose weight?
吉本斯以前
Augustus always had such...well
說到你的時候用詞都不太友好
not excatly nice things to say about you.
你什麼時候意識到他們都是在演戲的呢？
When did you realize it was all fake?
你是說剛剛這幾個搞笑演員麼
You mean the clown show?
你們那邊站了一個人 戴著幾千塊的名牌耳機
You had a guy over there wearing thousand dollars beats...
卻在賣假冒商品的小店邊徘徊
where you can buy a knock-off for half the price.
還有個女士 跑著趕著上一班兩小時後才出發的公交車
Or the lady that was running to catch a bus that doesn't leave for two hours.
還有一個警衛 拿著外國貨幣買汽水喝
Or the security guard over there buying a soda with foreign currency?
你知道最搞笑的地方是什麼嗎？
You know what the kicker was?
就是那個跟我大談美好生活的老頭
Clearence from "It's a Wonderful Life".
拿著包炸彈坐在我邊上
You know the nice old man who sat down next to me with the bag of bombs?
真湊巧 他怎麼知道我會說英語呢
Just happen he knows I spoke English.
下次演戲時注意這些小細節哦
Go figure.
- 那槍裏的子彈可能是真的啊 - 那你們穿的防彈衣估摸著也是真的
- Bullets could have been real. - And the body armour would have been real.
我不知道你是何方神聖 但我可不喜歡被人這麼耍
I do not know you, but I don't like to be tested.
吉本斯從來都不相信你的死訊 他一直在找你
Gibbons never believed you were dead. He never stopped looking for you.
- 真是個忠誠的朋友 - 你肯定是開玩笑吧
- Hell of a friend. - Yeah. Well, the joke's on him.
- 我們之間從來都算不上朋友 - 相信我 他要是在場 並不會想笑
- Because we were never friends. - Trust me, he is not laughing.
而且 他估計再也笑不出來了
Nor will he ever again for that matter.
我從沒見過身手這麼敏捷的人
I had never seen anything like it.
他們心狠手辣 人擋殺人佛擋殺佛
This group is lethal, and they do not care who or what gets it their way.
繼續看看後面的資料 希望你會感興趣
I was hoping you will be interested in headlining the next five card.
距離9米 落差27米
30 feet across, 90 feet down.
穿破了7厘米厚的防彈玻璃？
3 inches security glass?
還沒有借助繩子 降落傘等工具
No ropes, no line, no parachute.
怎麼說也得來一點定向爆破吧
I bet they had a blast.
我們使用了世界上所有的身份數據庫進行面部識別 結果一無所獲
We ran facial identification on every database in the world. Nothing.
他們甚至沒有因為超速被抓拍過
Not even a match on a speeding ticket.
他們就是現代社會的幽靈
They are ghosts, in a day and age where
用那些東西根本找不到他們
that kind of thing's almost impossible.
這麼說吧
Okay
你也知道我不願意為你們這些政府人員工作
You get that I do not work for suits.
我為什麼要破壞我平靜的生活 去管你們的事呢？
What makes you think I want to ruin all my life for?
我知道
No...
如果你不願意為我賣命
if you do not want do it for me ...
至少也得為吉本斯報仇吧
do it for Gibbons.
我們的祖國需要您 凱奇先生 極限特工項目需要你出一份力
Your country needs you. Mr. Cage. The Triple-X program needs you
是時候拿出你的愛國之心 為國效力了
It's time to be a patriot.
是不是愛國者還不是你們這些當官的說了算？
By whose definition?
上次我愛國的時候 我吃了三枚子彈
Last time I was patriotic, I got three strikes.
只有一個人相信我還沒死
And there was only one man who believed in the underdog.
愛國之心已經遠去 這個世界裏儘是些暴徒和暴君
Patriotism is dead. There are only rebels and tyrants now.
所以你到底打算怎麼辦
So which are you?
我還是干回老本行咯
I am Triple-X.
XXX特工 歡迎回來
Welcome back, Triple-X.
你要去哪？
Where are you going?
- 倫敦 - 為啥？
- London. - Why? What's in London?
去找獵魔人
Ghosthunter.
順便把我的皮衣拿回來
And possibly a fur coat.
我都快忘了上面的景色有多美了
I have forgotten how beautiful the view is up here.
你又穿回了你的皮衣啊
Oh, see you found your coat.
是啊 當時你答應的放在你這保管啊
Oh you promise take care of it for me
是啊 我這不是保管的挺好嘛
And I did
我要找一個人
I'm looking for someone.
我們啥時候變成業務合作關繫了
Since when did we have a business relationship?
你知道我不能再碰電腦了 要不然他們又得把我抓起來了
You know, I get caught even touching a computer, my hour is up for 20.
看看信息 報個價吧
Name your price.
我知道你最擅長幹這個了
You know I'm good for it.
這麼寶貴的信息 可是無價的呢
Information like this doesn't have a price.
安思麗 一切皆有價
Ainsley, everything has a price.
如果你覺得你手藝生疏 搞不定的話
Now, if you don't think you can pull it off,
直接說就好了 我能理解你的
if you'd lost your edge, just tell me and I'll understand.
凱奇 你知道我現在在想什麼嗎？
You know what it is, Cage?
你說
What?
我以前覺得你是老大
I used to think you are the man
現在我發現
But now...
我也不確定 你可能也只是給他打工罷了
I do not know, maybe I feel that you're working for him
哈哈
Come on
我是一個人來的 沒人知道我在哪
Nobody knows I'm here.
你也知道 我不是那種守不住秘密的人
And you know how I am about keeping secrets.
就算你說的沒錯 我也得考慮一下國際刑警的那些竊聽器啊
So you say, but Interpol got these listening bugs.
肉眼基本看不到竊聽器藏在哪
I mean, they're practically invisible, real MI-6 kind of shit.
什麼皮下監聽器之類的
Disappear under your skin, underarms ...
甚至你的私處你可能藏著竊聽器喲
tied around your balls like a Christmas bow.
那你倒是好好檢查一下我呀
unwrap me, then
你知道嗎 研究發現 發生性關係的情侶中
You know, studies have proven that sexual consummation irrevocably ruins ...
十對有九對關係會破裂
nine out of ten relationships.
那我們至少可以賭那10%嘛
Lucky for me, you love to gamble.
當然
Of course
不行
not.
我會讓我的朋友們好好招待你的
My friends on the other hand, adores the ***
是麼？
***
這可真是為國效力啊
The things I do for my country.
想找他們的信息就像大海撈針一樣難哦
Like finding needles in a stack of needles.
雖然你已多年不親自上陣
Even though you are shackled by the queen...
你還是這麼給力啊
you're still the best of the world.
多謝誇獎
Thank you.
聽我一句勸 別蹚渾水
Do yourself a favor. Burn this.
我聽到了不少消息 這些傢伙本事可不小
The words that I hear out in the streets, these ghosts caused real kind of trouble
身手不凡 資金充足
They got training and they got funding ...
沒人擋得住他們的
and they've got no problem running over anyone who gets in their way.
我明白了 你是怕我受傷吧
I can see you worry that I may get hurt.
我是怕你會英勇"犧牲"哦
I worry that you might get dead.
你怕失去我 我很感動
You know, I'm touched you can't imagine a world without me in it.
要是沒你在身邊 那該多無聊啊
It would be less fun.
該說的我都說了 你看著辦
That's all I'm saying.
你要找的那些人現在在菲律賓
Your ghosts are hanging out in Philippines.
我就猜到了他們會躲在那邊
Figures they go to the Pacific.
估計正躲在孤島上狂歡吧 一般人還找不到他們
Some jungle rave that's off the grid.
你怎麼這麼快就搞到情報了
How the hell did you find them so quickly?
這可是我出賣色相換來的情報
Undercover work.
你把"潘多拉魔盒"放在哪了？
Where is it? What did you do with Pandora's Box?
藏在安全的地方了
It's in a safe place.
這和我們計劃中的不一樣
That was not part of the plan.
我們都共事這麼些年了 臨時改變計劃也不是一次兩次了 你還覺得很驚訝？
After all these years, you are still shocked when I improvise?
我驚訝的是 這與我們的任務目標不一致 我們的目的是銷毀它
No. But the mission was to destroy it.
這麼跟你說吧 任務目標改了
It turns out there's a new mission.
我們能利用這玩意達成我們的目標 所以我不打算毀掉它了
I am not going to destroy the one thing that I can use to get what we want.
- 全世界都在追捕我們 項！ - 讓他們來啊！
- The world is looking for us, Xiang! - Let them come!
你總是在意那些走卒
You are worried about pawn sacrifice.
而我 眼裏只有對面的國王
I get my eye on the king.
現在問題在於
That's the problem.
你把皇后給忘了
You forgot the queen.
皇家空軍基地 英國 萊肯希思
Royal Air Force Station Lakenheath, United Kingdom
在你成功的挫敗了"無政府99"的陰謀之後 上頭給了吉本斯很大一筆錢
After your success taking down Anarchy 99, Gibbons was handed a blank check.
話說他當時
Which is the long way of saying ...
還給你配了一輛新車吧
he got you a new ride
凱奇 在你"死後" 世界可是發生了翻天覆地的變化啊
The world went to another place since your death Cage.
什麼無人機 導彈干擾儀
On board drones, anti-air countermeasures ...
戰機也添置了超大油箱 載油量可供飛機繞地球飛行三圈
and fuel tanks big enough to circumnavigate the globe three times ...
無需著陸加油
without even landing.
你可以把厚大衣脫下來了 我保證這裏沒人敢偷你的衣服
You can check your coat. I promise you no one will dare steal it.
但我可不敢保證衣服會不會自己長腳自己溜出去
I can guarantee it can't walk off on its own.
士兵們 剛剛我跟你們說10分鐘後起飛 你們現在還有7分鐘準備
Wheels up in ten, boys! which means you are already 7 minutes behind.
她平時講話一直都這麼逗的？
Is she always so much fun or just on special occasions?
難怪我們的國家負債纍纍
No wonder our country in debt trillions of dollars.
就抓幾個壞人真的用得上這些先進的玩意麼？
Do you really need all these gadgets to get the bad guys?
說實話 大部分我們都用不上
We do not need any of it.
有了這些有趣的玩具 抓捕過程才會更好玩呀
But it make catching more fun.
我去 這不是桑德·凱奇麼！
Xander Cage! Holy shit!
終於見到本人了 真刺激！
Live concert in one night only. This is crazy!
我曾經參加過槍炮玫瑰的演唱會
I was at Coachella and Guns N'Roses got back together.
但是這可比那演唱會刺激多了
but this is way cooler
嚴格意義上說 我當時不在演唱會現場 但是
Well, I was not actually there, but ...
我看了那演唱會的全過程呢 你懂我的意思吧？
I heard about it, you know?
我的天 我真是個話癆
I'm so talking. Oh my God.
抱歉 我一開口就停不下來
Sorry, it's a bad habit. I get started and then ...
- 根本停不下來 然後... - 深呼吸
- I can not stop and I can not ... - Breathe.
慢慢來 你要是嗆著了我可以給你人工呼吸的
Take your time. I know mouth-to-mouth if necessary.
看看你結實的雙臂
Are you kidding me with those guns?
你特麼簡直就是個終結者啊！
You look like the fucking Terminator!
不是那個第一代的終結者
I'm not talking about the first Terminator ...
而是那個第二代的 回去殺第一代的那個
but the second Terminator goes back to kill the first terminator.
就是可以融化成液態金屬的那個二代終結者
It is the liquid metal guy.
克拉裏奇特工與吉本斯共事過 她將為你的行動提供技術支持
Agent Claridge worked closely with Gibbons. She will handle support for the operation.
像你這樣的頂級特工肯定很需要我的幫助
And a guy like you needs a lot of support.
你有多重來著？220磅？230磅？
What are you like? 220? 230?
總不至於250磅吧？
Be honest. 250 is the hardest max for my swing.
- 怎麼可能 - 我就開個玩笑
- Oh come on. - I'm kidding.
偷偷告訴你 我的安全詞是"金橘"
It's not like I have a safe word or anything, it is "kumquat".
定這個詞的時候我也沒想太多
I never really think about it.
"金橘"
kumquat
你呢？
What about you?
我的詞典裏沒有"不安全"
"Not safe" isn't in my vocabulary.
那是 你可以無所不能的桑德·凱奇呀
Touche, you're the Xander Cage.
不管你需要什麼 貝奇在1小時內都能給你弄到
Anything you need, Becky can source it within an hour.
除了某些違法藥物
Except for any sort of illegal drugs.
那些我15分鐘就能搞到
Those I'll have in 15 minutes.
開個玩笑啦
Kidding.
如果你需要的是...你就不用來找我了
But if you need a *** of purple ***, I'm not the girl to ask.
凱奇 跟我來 我來給你介紹一下你的地麵團隊
Okay, Cage, follow me. I'll introduce you to your ground team.
- 謝謝啦 貝奇 - 沒事
- Thank you, Becky. - Of course.
"金橘"
kumquat
我們可以看紅牛怪咖秀了
Here comes the Red Bull freak show.
桑德·凱奇 這位是保羅
Xander Cage, I want you to meet Paul...
多諾萬
Donovan.
保羅·多諾萬上校
Captain Paul Donovan.
我在電視上見過你
I know you. I saw you on TV.
總統給你頒發了一枚獎章 當時挺神氣的吧？
The president gave him a medal. It must be pretty cool, right?
你們肯定經歷了不少大風大浪
You guys must have some seriously cool stories to tell.
見識了不少大場面吧
must have seen a lot.
我想問問你們當中
I wonder:
有多少人在越野自行車玩過自由式三連後滾翻的？
How many have ever pulled a free-style triple back flip?
有人這麼玩過麼？
On a BMX bike before? All of you?
不 我們很少跟自行車打交道
No, we do not play on bicycles.
是麼
Oh, you do not play on bikes?
那有沒有人在雪崩的時候
any of you ever carved an R4
玩過滑雪板呢？
On a snowboard ...
滾滾飛雪追在你屁股後面 真是刺激啊
while an avalanche is on your booty?
我們是前途無量的特種兵 可不是什麼玩雜技的懶人
We're soldiers, hotshot, not slackers.
好吧 那你們肯定在東歐
Okay, but you all ...
用標準的軍用降落傘設備玩過
have HALO jumps over Eastern Europe ...
高空跳傘 我沒說錯吧
using a standard-issued armor dempolyed parachute system. Am I right?
從來沒有的事
No.
你個蠢貨 我們可沒你的閒心玩那些雜技呢
We're not all jack up on Mountain Dew and Red Bull, you asshole.
你是在哪找到這傢伙的？
Where did you find this guy?
凡事都有第一次 祝你們玩的開心喲
Oh there is the first time for everything.
你這是在幹什麼？我簡直不敢相信我的眼睛
What did you just do? I can not believe this shit.
我才不會跟這幾個豬隊友合作呢
I am not gonna have clowns watch my back.
那我你倒是說說看 你願意跟誰合作
I know I'm gonna regret asking you this, but who would you trust?
這個電話也就你一個人知道
You know no one has this number.
最近都在忙啥呢
So what do you up to these days?
我麼 我就四處走走
Me? Moving in odds.
阿黛爾·沃夫 致人骨折數量最高紀錄保持著
ADELE WOLFF UNOFFICIAL RECORD FOR MOST BROKEN BONES
使命召喚遊戲昵稱：LADY_BONER
CALL OF DUTY HANDLE: LADY_BONER
最喜歡的電影：生來自由
FAVORITE MOVIE Born Free
- 上上上！ - 舉起手來！
- Go in, go! - Show me your hands!
走出車來！
Get out of the car, now!
這場景彷彿似曾相識啊！
It was like that when I got here.
泰尼森·托奇 特技駕駛員 職業生涯中198次事故
TENNYSON TORCH Stunt Driver 198 Lifetime CRASHES
聲稱曾被外星人綁架兩次
Claims he has been abducted by aliens TWICE.
陪伴他最長時間的物品：他的牙套
LONGEST RELATIONSHIP: his Rugby Mouthguard
除非你是特技運動員 否則不能進入
Nobody gets in unless you are X-Games participant!
聽到沒有？
Do you hear me?
那裏有個人直接過去了
That guy got through!
最近過得怎樣？
What, Nyjah?
二位小姐好啊
Ray and Burrito.
最近過得怎樣 兄弟？
Chad, how are you, bro?
羅伯塔 我們待會再聊
Roberta. I'll see you later.
尼奇 真名:尼克斯 周 綽號：兜帽哥
NICKY NICKS ZHOU ALIAS "THE HOOD"
曾經同一個晚上約會過泰勒斯威夫特和嘎嘎小姐
DATED TAYLOR SWIFT AND LADY GAGA ... IN THE SAME NIGHT
特殊技能：調節聚會氣氛
SPECIAL SKILL fun to be around.
槍法一流 身手敏捷
The good, the bad, the extreme...
還有一個徹頭徹尾的瘋子
and the completely insane
我就願意跟他們這樣的人一起並肩作戰
This is the team I can work with.
簡單的給你們介紹一下情況
I'll make it easy for you.
這四個人 是大壞蛋
These four assholes: very bad guys.
潘多拉魔盒 就是個不好的東西
Pandora's Box: very bad thing.
把你們送到馬尼拉後 你們自己坐船去他們藏身的島上
You will land at Manila and you will requsition your own transportation to the island.
為啥不直接丟一個核彈把那個島轟平麼
Why don't we just nuke this bitch in oil bean and car, eh?
這麼說吧 這個"潘多拉魔盒"是獨一無二的
Pandora's Box is one of a kind
我們得把它毫髮無損的弄回來
It needs to be recovered intact.
為啥？它具體有啥功能？
Why? What does it do?
- 精神控制？ - 就是它殺死了吉本斯
- Brainwave scrambler? - It killed Gibbons.
你們只需要知道這麼多 剩下的均為機密信息
All you need to know. The rest is classfied.
肯定是精神控制儀
Brainwave scrambler
我覺著吧
Do you smell that?
這些穿西裝的還是那種老調調 什麼機密不機密的
It smells like the same shit in a different suit.
你應該知道"飛盤遊戲"的玩法吧
You think a dog knows how to work "Frisbee"?
主人說"去撿" 小狗就會跑過去把飛盤叼回來
The master says "fetch," and the bitch listens.
你嘴裏叼著飛盤的樣子 一定很性感
You'd look so sexy with a Frisbee in that mouth.
親愛的 我可不是在跟你說笑
Sweetheart, this is not a game.
你們現在都是我手下的士兵
You're all my soldiers now.
- 我可不是士兵 我只是個舞廳控場員罷了 - 我們看起來像士兵麼？
- I'm not a soldier, I'm a parlour. - Do we look like soldiers?
怎麼可能
Oh hell no.
- 我們你的士兵都丟在東歐那邊了 - 你為啥不把她也順便丟下去呢？
- I drop your soldiers over Eastern Europe. - Why did you leave lassie behind?
這是我負責的行動 你們都得聽我的！
This is my operation! You will listen to me.
看起來這會已經沒必要開下去了
The meeting is over.
那麼 林肯女士 接下去要怎麼辦？
Other than that, Mrs. Lincoln ... how was the play?
這個是超級護甲
That's super strength body armor.
你得把這個皮帶系到
We got to tighten the belt ...
這邊
Over here.
再到這邊
I got this on.
你是我的操作員麼？
What are you, my handler?
你需要我幫你什麼 我就是什麼
I am whatever you need.
我能搞定一切問題
I can handle anything.
再把這繫緊一些
And I got a tight grip.
順便說一句 我不出外勤的
And just for you know, I'm not a field agent.
我從沒出過外勤 從來沒有過
I do not go out in the field. Ever.
我覺得一名特工的樂趣 就在於外出行動
That's where all the fun is.
出門我會覺得很害怕
Fun scares me.
我怕見到槍
People scare me, guns scare me.
那些舞刀弄槍的真得把我嚇死 如果我被嚇著了 我就做不成我的本職工作了
People with guns really scare me, If I'm scared I can not do my job.
完成不好我的工作 就會有人犧牲 要是你們都犧牲了
And if I can't do my job, then people die. And if people die, who does my tech supporting?
我的技術支持還有什麼用
Literally no one.
但我會竭盡全力確保你的安全的
But I'll make sure to keep you safe.
想確保我的安全可不容易喲
It ain't easy to keep me safe.
我最喜歡這個新玩意了
Yes, these badboys are my favorites.
它們叫"鐵錘" 可用於地面肉搏戰
They called Exogloves . *** new ground combat initiative.
氣泵驅動 可將拳擊力量加到4倍
pneumatic pistons drive the gears. qualdruple the speed, and power of the punches.
別動那個
No no.
這個是多頻道信號干擾儀
This is a multi-stage signal disrupter
極其容易損壞
It is very, very breakable
你能告訴我泛美航空103航班墜毀
Can you tell me the real reason behind the crash?
背後的真相麼？
Of Pan Am Flight 103 over Lockerbie?
可以
Yes.
你應該讀過那些機密文件吧
You're one of them, right?
親 別亂來
Hey easy. Rocky.
我跟你說 這玩意能在飛機上
I wasn't kidding when I say it because the force of these badboys
搞個大洞
to cut a hole in a fucking plane.
我再四處走走 看看還會不會有別的地方出亂子
Keep walking around. What can possibly go wrong?
- 我就愛玩點刺激的 - 好啊 你真行
- That's my style, though. - Yes, good. glad to hear.
你知道麼 這個...
You know? Actually...
我跟你說可以....
I would rather if you...
真棒 你動手能力不錯啊
That's refreshing. You actually know what you are doing down there.
是啊
Yes, that's what she said.
卡拉莫安島 菲律賓
Caramoan Islands PHILIPPINES
讓他們過去
Let them pass.
兄弟 需要什麼？
Need something, man?
我聽說這是個可以讓我的船員避避風頭的好地方
I heard this is a perfect place to disappear for a few days ...
聽說不問出身 不問來頭
for my crew, no questions asked
付個好價錢 你就可以把我這當你家了
My home is your home, if you pay good price.
很好
Perfect.
泰尼森！
Tennyson!
我覺著你肯定喜歡這些玩意 我手裏有這片地方最好的槍
Figure you like this. I just happen to have the best *** in the South Pacific.
留下30% 我給你來一個豪華住宿套餐
30% of the top gets you a finest hospitality package.
30%？我是不是還能帶上幾個椰子 帶走幾個女孩子逍遙快活幾個晚上？
30% of the top? Can I get the girls for a weekend and two coconuts?
最多10%吧
Ten percent.
10%？你在逗我笑？
10%?
你還是去別的地方吧
I think looking the other island without laws, it happens all the time.
你這麼辦 掉頭 回你的破船 滾遠點吧
I'll tell you what to do. You turn around, go get your boat. You kiss my ass.
等會 我跟他們商量一下
It's okay. Hanging on.
你覺得怎麼樣
What do you think?
就這麼定了！
You talked me into it!
18%吧
Eighteen percent!
當我這是舊貨市場呢？
You think this is a flea market?
當我這是賣破舊電視假手錶的雜貨鋪呢？
You think we neighborhoods sell televisions and fake watches or something like that?
兄弟 你腦子沒問題吧？
What's wrong with you, friend?
再多給你一點吧 22.5%如何？
All right. 22.5%.
你要怎麼給我半把槍？
How do I give the half?
很簡單
Twenty two...
喏 給你半把
and a half.
兄弟 進來吧
Hi man. Enjoy the party.
我就喜歡你這種作風
I like your style, man.
不管發生什麼 待在船上
Stay on that boat, no matter what.
阿黛爾 尼克斯 跟我來
Adele, Nicks!
各位 打開你們的耳機
Well, guys, keep your ear bugs in.
像往常一樣 阿黛爾 你爬到高處觀察全局
Like always, Adele, you're my eyes in the sky.
尼克斯 你就四處走走
Nicks, you are gonna show how we did.
看那邊
You got this?
天天就知道看那些東西
You just watch.
請把我的衣服寄存一下吧
Can you keep this behind the bar, please?
您要喝點什麼？
What can I get you?
給我來一杯蔓越莓蘇打水
A cranberry club soda.
來兩份
Make that two.
- 謝謝 - 不客氣
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
保持警惕
Stay focus.
好吧
Really?
桑德·凱奇重出江湖啦
Xander Cage. Back in action.
我只是隱退了一小段時間好麼
Did I ever leave?
發現目標了
Spot that clown.
比我想像的容易多了 他在四處晃蕩呢
Easier than we expected. Drinks all around.
有人跟來了 去解決他
That's him.
又到了我最喜歡的
***. douche bag hunting season.
狙擊傻瓜時間了
my favorite.
這麼早就開槍 不太好吧
It is too early in the evening to slay someone.
- 我去搞定他 - 我去
- Let me fix it. - Oh come on.
我一槍不就完事了麼
The *** doesn't deserves a bullet? I think he does.
感覺大家還不夠熱情啊
Is this a party or a funeral?
大家跳起來啊！
Either way, somebody is going to hang up tonight!
跟你說吧 他很會調節氣氛的
Told you he was fun having around.
最開始我以為你們是特種部隊的
At first I thought Special Forces.
但你身上的文身挺多
But your inks all wrong.
中情局的？
CIA?
他們估計會直接派無人機把我們轟成灰
They would send in a drone to bomb us to hell.
軍情六處的？
MI6?
感覺你沒有他們特工身上的氣質
You are not kind of subtlety they prefer
你知道來島上的人都是來避風頭的
You know the men who come to this island. They're on the run.
都是躲避追捕之類的
Hiding from the world.
你肯定不是那號人
But not you.
你肯定不是來尋一個藏身之處的
You are not here to hide.
你是來找東西的
You're looking for someone.
你怎麼就知道 我還沒找到我想找的東西呢？
Who says I haven't already find it?
你這是在恐嚇我？
Do you want to scare me?
恐懼能讓我們的對話更加有趣
a little tremble will be nice.
那麼
Well...
如果你覺得你能把我嚇走的話
considering one tremble to make you run away from here...
我警告你 最好別輕舉妄動
I'd say I'm close enough.
喲 看上去你不是那種賢妻良母嘛
Does this means you're not making any breakfast in the morning?
我就動手又何妨？
I'd say a couple of inches off.
看起來陷入了僵局啊
Bit of a stalemate.
你要是先把槍放下 就能結束僵局了
Not if you drop the gun
我不是壞人
I'm not the bad guy.
哪怕你是好人 我也不信你
I don't believe in good guys.
賽琳娜？
Serena?
他是誰
Who is he?
我們才剛剛認識
We just met.
除非我們中哪個人決定打破僵局
But we got along famously until somebody ...
要麼我們就一直這麼僵持下去吧
decided to interrupt
按著島上的小路走下去
stick to the path
親愛的 拿好你的槍
Here honey
你會看到島上的亂墳地
There are a lot of unmarked graves on the island.
我打賭 把這花襯衫賣給你的小販 估計就埋在那裏吧
And I'll bet whoever sold you that shirt is one of them.
你要在這打探多久？
How long do you intend to push a look?
在我找到我想要的東西前 我都不會走的
Until I get what I came for.
所以你到底想找什麼
which is what exactly?
先來幾杯烈酒再說
A damn stiff drink.
來吧 我們來談重點 你就是來找這個的吧
So, let's be real and talk about what we all really want.
沒錯
I am only here for that.
我是這麼想的 你們可以放下它 毫髮無損的離開 除非你想繼續我們之前那麼舞刀弄槍的
In my minds, you guys can walk away nicely. unless you want to continue our foreplay?
像那樣的力量不屬於任何人
Power like that doesn't belong in anyone's hands.
我這也是臨時改變計劃喲
Just improvising.
我沒看錯吧？手榴彈？這不是上世紀90年代的東歐的玩法麼？
Seriously? A grenade? What is this? Eastern Europe in 1990s?
這麼復古 他是不是以後準備發傳真呢？
Next, he's gonna send you a fax.
你願意我拿到這個東西
So you are willing to kill?
而大開殺戒麼
Just to keep that for yourself?
問題不是這麼問的
That's a wrong question to ask.
正確的問題是？
What's the right question?
"你願意為它而死麼？"
"Are you willing to die for it?"
一枚手雷 三條性命
One grenade, three people.
這就有趣了
I like the odds.
兩枚手雷 三條性命
Two grenades, three people.
這就更有趣了
I'm loving these odds.
你有沒有過那種經歷 你失血過多 睜開雙眼 周圍的一切都是紅色的
Have you never bled so much that when you open your eyes, all you see is red?
你在戰場裏摸爬滾打
When you have fought in wars on every continent.
桑德 下命令吧 我可以兩槍搞定他們
Come on X, just say the word, Let me put both these two arseholes out in the pasture.
只有死亡
Except death.
人是何等的脆弱
Our bodies are such fragile.
讓我開槍吧
Let me shoot him.
死亡有時就在
Death sometimes just...
不經意間襲來
sneak on you
我已經很久沒玩過"燙手山芋"了
It's been a while since I played hot potato.
我當時躺在病床上
I'm in a hospital bed.
神志不清 奄奄一息
I'm barely conscious, delirious. Drowning in my own blood.
我的腦子裏盤旋著一個聲音 "今天就是...
And all I can hear myself to think is "Today is the day"
"今天就是你死的那一天"
"Today is the day you die"
真是個感人的故事
I'm touched.
能把我的外套拿來麼
Can I have my jacket?
後來有一個人來看望我 跟我講了一個
There is a man comes along, tells me the story ...
關於加州旱災的故事
about a drought in California.
還提到了什麼滑板和游泳池
About skateboards and swimming pools.
其中講到了一個叫桑德·凱奇的人
About a man named Xander Cage.
我的天 他也是一個極限特工啊
Oh shit. He is Triple-X.
我聽說他已經死了
I heard he was dead.
是麼？
Is he?
我們都是極限特工
We are all Triple-X.
只是目標各有不同
We just have different agenda.
她是想著銷毀它
She wants to destroy it.
我是決定將它化為己用
I'm going to use it.
我是不可能讓你把它帶回國安局的
And I will be damned if I am gonna let you take it back to NSA
機密文件
Secret
現在派對才像樣嘛
Now it's a party.
要出大亂子嘍
Shit's about to go down.
你覺得這很好玩？
You think that is for fun?
把音樂關掉！
Turn off the music!
關掉！
Stop it!
所有人舉起手來！
Everybody hands up!
快！
Now!
都趴到地上
On the floor!
誰先動 我就崩了誰
First person to move, first person to die!
我動了
I moved.
我又動了
I moved again.
我怎麼還活著呢
I am still alive.
閉嘴吧 蠢貨
Shut up, "hero"!
好吧
All right.
我們來好好談談
Let's do this.
別動
Do not move!
我手上有你想要的東西
Well, I actually have what you want.
你不就是想要"潘多拉魔盒"嘛
Pandora's box?
它就在我這呢
I got it right here.
但是你聽好了
But you're wrong though.
你想把它從我這拿走 只怕你也活不成了
You take it from me, and you die first.
還有你自以為能保證你安全的大兵們
Then Lieutenant Leningrad, thinks he got you back
兩位大兵
Then the two Ivans by the door.
吧檯那邊的一位
Moscow Mule by the bar.
台階上的那位大兵 都要戰死了
Then Igor on the stairs.
你想不想來試試看？
See where we are going with this?
那些都是後話了
But none of that matters.
我已經說過了
Because like I said ...
你要是想奪走它 只怕你也活不了嘍
if you take this from me, you die first.
不管你是死是活 我都能搞到它
I will take it from you, dead or alive.
如果你死的時候攥的太緊 那我們就把的手切下來一起帶走
If you hold it too tight, they cut your arm off.
那我們走著瞧
Suit yourself.
幹掉一個
Leningrad.
兩個
Hello Ivan.
三個
The other Ivan.
四個
Goodbye, Moscow Mule.
這是第五個 桑德 我又救你一命了
Igor. It's another one you owe me. X.
槍法可以的
Read between the lines.
泰尼森 你是不是要來支援一下
Tennyson! Some back will be nice.
來支援一下我們啊！快來！
Some back will be nice! Come on man!
桑德叫我不管如何都待在船上
X says I stay on the boat.
他就隨口一說 快來吧！
That was before the goddamn Russian invasion takes down ,man!
桑德說了 我不管如何都待在船上
X says stay on the boat.
你要跟我玩這個？
Do you want to play?
那種力量不屬於任何人
That doesn't belong in anyone's hands.
想要的話就來搶吧
If you want it. Come and get it.
這樣真的好麼？
Was that necessary?
吉本斯正希望我們這麼做呢
It's what Gibbons would have wanted.
桑德！
X!
X.
出大事了 又一個衛星掉下來了
It happened again. Another satellite fell.
要不要加入我們？
How's working as a team?
吉本斯肯定希望我們這些極限特工並肩作戰呢
That's what Gibbons would have wanted.
你來不來
You in?
發生在奧林匹克體育館的爆炸震動了整個莫斯科
An explosion inside the Olympic Stadium rocks Moscow
七位工作人員已確認遇難
Seven workers are now confirmed dead.
25位受傷
With at least 25 others injured in this senseless act of violence.
根據五角大樓公佈的信息
A source inside the Pentagon says ...
可能有人把失控的衛星作為武器
a rouge satellite may have been used as a weapon.
按這麼說來 "潘多拉魔盒"已經不再是機密咯
This means that Pandora's Box is not exactly classified.
幾分鐘前 一個匿名組織公佈了一段錄像
In a new video, released just moments ago, an anonymous group ...
宣稱他們有能力將衛星作為動能武器
is claiming to have the ability to use satellites as weapons. They claimed
他們說 "必須阻止破壞
quote "The violation of civil liberties of all citizens of the world ...
世界公民自由的暴行"
It is an atrocity that must be stopped "
在24小時內終止並取消世界上所有的間諜項目
Disable and dismantle all the world spy programs within the next 24 hours ...
否則我就幫你們墜毀這些間諜衛星 一次一個
or I will do it for you one satellite at a time.
目前共有30000枚衛星繞地球運行
There are 30,000 satellites orbiting the Earth at this moment.
我將會每24小時墜毀一個 直接世界各國滿足我的要求
I will drop one satellite every 24 hours until my demands are met.
在莫斯科的目擊者聲稱....
eyewitnesses in Moscow ...
- 你們是不是每次任務都要對付這種喪心病狂的混蛋？ - 當然不是
- Was this always part of mission to you? - Of course not.
桑德走後 吉布斯組織了新的極限特工隊 我們都是其中的成員
We were a new Triple-X team Gibbons created.
當時我們發現了一個高級別的情報官員正試圖私自操縱衛星
We discovered a high-level intelligence officer who was trying to manipulate satellites.
在我們把他揪出來之前
And even before we could unmask him
吉布斯遇害了
Gibbons was killed.
所以你一直都知道 他們都是極限特工
So you knew they were Triple-X all along
我需要你在執行任務時保持客觀
I needed you to retain a sense of objectivity.
我不太明白 如果我之前毀掉了"潘多拉魔盒" 那莫斯科這個是什麼情況？
I don't understand. If I destroyed Pandora's Box. What happened in Moscow?
如果我沒錯的話
If I am right, which I am ...
這個盒子最多只能操縱一顆衛星
this box only had the ability to control one satellite.
你的意思是？
What does that mean?
我們一直在追蹤的只是一台原型機
It means we have been chasing a prototype.
- 恐怖分子手上的那台才是真貨？ - 沒錯
- And these guys have the real one? - Yes.
塞麗娜把我們給耍了
Serena played us like fools.
她背叛了我們
betrayed us.
別管她了 現在這亂子鬧得可不小
This is not about Serena. This is a war.
要麼我們想辦法阻止他們 要麼就眼睜睜的看著世界變成一片火海 這才是重點
And either we stop today or we watch the world burn tomorrow. can't lose focus on that.
你去哪了 咋動作這麼慢？
Where were you have you been? You stopped ***
去你丫的
Your mom says hi.
定位器安裝好了吧？沒被人發現吧？
tracker on board? Nobody saw you?
- 老闆 絕對萬無一失 - 很好
- No one ever sees me, boss - good.
這些高官掌控著太空中衛星的動向
These suits control every spy satellites in the sky.
一般來說 這些高官多久會坐在一起開會？
But, how often these seven men all sit in the same room together?
基本不會坐到一起吧
Almost never
如果需要收集他們的視網膜信息
And if you needed retinal scans ...
手機數據轉存記錄 生物特徵值
cellphone data dumps, biometrics of all the superpowers in the world...
你覺得誰最有可能做到這一點
Who would you target?
不是吧
Shit
你覺得誰最能毫不費力的收集到這些信息？
Who has that kind of power to actually set that in motion?
只怕你是懷疑錯人了 凱奇 別忘了 可是我去找你的喲
You're pissing up the wrong tree, Cage. I came looking for you, remember?
混蛋 我們是不是要來算算賬？
Oh, asshole.  We are going to have problems?
行啊 跳傘玩的愉快麼？
Oh no problem. How was your trip?
我心裏在算點東西呢
I'm just doing the maths.
是麼 你在算什麼？
Oh yeah? What maths?
距離除以降落速度
Air velocity divided by distance.
所以當我把你送下去的時候 搜救隊
So when I stuff you down the toilet, the search and rescue...
知道該去哪把你們這幫廢物救回來
know where to find you between China and North Korea.
夥計 你就繼續放屁吧
keep talking shit, man.
走著瞧吧 大兵
Hold that thought, GI Joe.
往回倒
Roll it back
再倒一點
A little more.
more
再倒一點 暫停
A little more. stop.
看這裏 當項撞破玻璃跳進來的時候
Okay, when Xiang broke the window ...
只有一個人波瀾不驚
He is the only one that did not flinch.
我需要馬上同總統通電話
I need the president on the phone immediately
那可是塊量子屏啊 別寫在上面 擦不掉啊!
That's not gonna scrub off. You know that right? It was a quantum screen!
原來這麼些年 中情局的局長一直想毀滅世界啊
It seems that the director of the CIA has been trying to destroy the world for years.
總統把處理這個混蛋的事務全權交給我們了
We have carte blanche to track this son of bitch down
你們中有人知道下一步應該怎麼辦嗎？
Do any of you know how to do it?
就用我和項在紐約定位到"潘多拉魔盒"的辦法吧
The same way Xiang and I found Pandora's Box in New York.
衛星環繞地球運行 因此它需要定期與衛星重新建立連接
Pandora's box needs to be reconnecting itself because of the satellites orbit.
抱歉 我需要操作一下
Excuse me.
我們只需要追蹤一個主要信號
All what we need to do is to track down the main signals.
然後我們可以大致定位到信號源 誤差不超過32千米
and then we can approximate its location within a 20 mile radius.
世界這麼大 這傢伙哪都沒去
Of all the places in the world ...
就藏在底特律？
this fruit choose Detroit?
莫斯科的爆炸震驚了整個世界
The blasts did take place in Moscow, but they were felt around the world.
今天早上 莫斯科爆炸事故的遇難人數迅速上升
In the morning, *** the death toll of Moscow's tragedy has rised.
我覺得是不是大家都在鼓動政府取消監聽項目啊
Let me guess. Everyone's jumping at the chance to dismantle their spy program.
不
No.
他們都太蠢了 不知道莫斯科的爆炸只不過是虛張聲勢罷了
The world is too stupid to realize that Moscow was a bluff.
極限特工們 你們將會駐紮在一個國安局的安全屋
Okay, Triple-X, you will base at an NSA safe house.
貝奇負責協調你們的通訊 並準備好信號干擾儀
Becky will coordinate your bug communications, and have the signal disrupter on standby.
兄弟 我為了救你的命 都把船開到岸上了
Mate, when I crashed the boat on shore to save your life ...
隨你這麼說咯 兄弟
Whatever bro
你覺得嚴格意義上 那能算我特技生涯的第199次事故麼
Do you think that counts as crash #199 for me? You know, officially?
嚴格意義上來說 你真是個瘋子
Officially, you're deranged
設備還真是齊全啊
Cool.
我們會在城市裏設置一個三角定位系統
We will set up a triangulated signal tracking system around the city
貝奇確認好它的準確位置後 你們就開始行動
When Becky locks in its exact location, we make our move.
你呢 你會參與行動麼？
What about you? How did you get involved in all this?
我曾經爬了個摩天輪 被抓起來判了一年
I dangled the skyscraper, and go to a year jail for it.
這也違法？
Jail?
似乎判的重了點
Seems excessive.
那玩意差不多有30層樓高
The *** was 30 storeys tall.
錄像發到Youtube上收穫兩百萬點擊了
Two million hits on YouTube.
我只在監獄裏呆了半年
And I served only half the sentence.
別急 讓我猜猜接下來的情節 吉本斯去救你了？
Let me guess. Gibbons to the rescue.
他說像我這麼有才的人關在監獄裏可惜了
He said a lion like me doesn't belong in any kind of cage.
我離開極限特工項目後 也畫了個紋身
I got mine after I left NSA.
- 你手腕上那個是在哪畫的？ - 倫敦
- What about that one your wrist? - London.
2009年的時候我徒手攀爬了倫敦眼
In 2009 climbed the Millennium Wheel.
一絲不掛哦
Naked.
- 沒穿衣服？ - 對的
- Naked? - Yeah.
這是我高中時畫的
High school.
天！
Oh no!
我們總有一些比較尷尬的時刻
We all have our embarrassing moments.
你身上的那個紋身是什麼來頭？
What about that sexy one?
你是說這個嘛 鳳凰涅槃重生？
This? The phoenix out of the ashes.
在墨西哥的時候 畫了18個小時
18 hours in a chair in Mexico.
喝了不知道多少龍舌蘭酒才熬過去
drank my body in tequila to get through it.
這個紋身對我來說意義非凡
It is the most important one actually
因為正是那個時候我決定拯救世界
It is when I decided to change the world instead of ...
而不是摧毀它
rage against it.
找到他了 已經定位到"潘多拉魔盒"的位置了
We found him. We found Pandora's Box.
桑德 聽到了麼？
Xander, do you copy?
收到 派泰尼森過去
We are here. Okay, send Tennyson.
地址應該是國會街 東404號 他在頂樓
Looks like East 404, Congress streets. He is on the top floor.
選擇衛星
SELECT SATELLITE
已經探測到"潘多拉魔盒"發出的信號 我可以干擾它
I'm sure activity with Pandora's Box. I can jam signal
但持續不了太久 你們動作快點
but only a few minutes, so hurry.
趕過去 把那傢伙給解決了
You got to get there fast and take this guy down.
除非我們先找到他
Not if we find him first.
小心紅燈
Red light!
你知道吧 交通燈就是那些石油巨頭發明出來浪費油 增加利潤的
You know traffic signals are invented by big oil to waste fuel, drive up profits.
你說的都對 能不能麻煩你開慢點？小心！
If I say "yes", would you please slow down? Look out!
讓我猜猜看
Wait.
你這麼盯著我 是不是現在還不信任我？
Is this the part where you anticipate, then you got your eye on me, you don't trust me?
猜的不假
Welcome to the moment.
但還是給你點武器防身吧
Everyone needs back up.
停車！
Stop!
泰尼森？
Tennyson?
前面的路都堵死了
A gridlock.
就是那棟樓頂
There it is.
如果你遇到了什麼麻煩
If you run into trouble ...
按9號鍵
dial nine.
這是吉本斯留下的備用方案
It is an old Gibbons fail safe.
你搞砸了我的派對 搶走了我的舞伴
You crashed my party! stole my dance partner!
我跟你沒完
I will crash yours.
拖住他們
Have fun.
這可不是一場派對 這是一場競賽
This is not a party. This is a race.
- 你在想啥呢？ - 我在建斜坡呢
- What the hell think you are you doing? - building a ramp.
沖沖沖
Go go go.
滾出來 快點
out of car! get out!
- 你要幹什麼 - 快滾
- What are you doing? - Let's go!
他正試圖重連衛星
He is trying to reconnect.
各位 信號干擾只能持續很短的時間 馬上他就要選另一顆衛星了 你們要加快了
Guys, I can only jam the signal for so long before he chooses another satellite. You have to hurry.
我有個想法了
I have a plan.
抓緊嘍
Hold on!
這他媽聽起來可不是什麼好想法
"Hold on" is no goddamn a plan!
嗨
Hi.
你是不是在找我？
Are you looking for someone?
第200次碰撞事故！
That's 200!
來追我啊
Haha, come on.
桑德 你們得馬上趕到頂樓了 他正試圖連接另一顆衛星
No! Xander, you guys have to got to the top floor. He is trying to engage another satellite.
快點！
Hurry!
真是甕中捉鱉啊
fish in the barrel
點四五口徑手槍
45 U.S.P
彈容12發
12 round mag.
還有5發
five left
還有3發
Three.
外面究竟是什麼情況
What the hell is going on out there?
空了
Empty.
桑德已經過去了 找到目標 一槍斃命
I got Xander in! Find the target, light them up.
吉本斯一直說你會回來的
Gibbons thought you'd be back.
成為萬眾矚目的英雄
To be the hero we needed.
你把它帶回國安局
you take the box to NSA
一切就又回到了原點
we are right back to where we started.
真是感人啊
This is touching.
要是吉本斯在世 他肯定很高興看到你們兩個並肩作戰
Gibbons would be proud to see you two working together.
想把它拿走 桑德？
walking out of here, Xander.
想知道吉本斯為什麼而死麼？
you wanna know secret?
你是不是忘記塗除臭劑了？
You forgot to put deodorant on?
我之所以殺了吉本斯 是因為他是一個自大的混蛋
I killed Gibbons because he was a self-righteous prick.
找到機會開槍了麼
Do you have a shot?
阿黛爾 找到機會開槍了麼
Adele, do you have eyes on the target?
沒 正在切換熱能瞄準鏡
I am switching to the thermal.
我會讓衛星一個個從天而降
I was never going to stop downing satellites
誰也不能阻止我 你知道為什麼嗎 因為這個世界...
no matter what happened, you know why, because this world has turned ...
求你馬上找到目標
Please, please tell me you have a shot
媽的
Damn it.
他開了暖氣 全糊了
He has turned the heat up. I can't see shit
桑德 我看不清那邊的情況 熱能瞄準鏡不好使
X, can't see you guys. thermal is not good.
- 我說的對不對？ - 那邊一團糊 看不清
- Right? - I lost them in the heat.
你難道不知道這個世界的現狀麼
you want to see what's going on in this world?
- 想想看 換做是你 你要怎麼辦？ - 別急 我們好好談談
- What are you gonna do about it? - easy.
桑德 拖住他 我還沒找到機會
X. Keep him talking. I still don't have a shot
就是像我 像你們兩個 像吉本斯這樣的人把世界搞得一團糟
We made it that way, people like Gibbons and two of you. And me.
都是我們的錯
We made it that way.
試想一下 你一覺醒來發現世界都...
What's the point of getting up in the morning if you're not gonna reboot the world
你說的沒錯
right, okay, easy
世界上許多地方 數百萬人們掙扎著求生
There's a war out there, a world war for our survival.
你還不明白麼 他們的死毫無意義
You don't see it? Millions of people have died for nothing!
看樣子你又得欠我一命了
Read between the lines.
- 我說的難道不對麼？ - 跟你說句大實話
- Come on, isn't it right? - I'm going to be honest with you.
自從見到你以後 我一直有句話想說
What has been bugging me this whole time
貌似你的牙齒中間塞了點東西
is you have got something stuck in between your teeth.
- 你說啥 扯什麼淡呢？ - 我是認真的
- What? What the hell are you talking about? - I'm serious.
你腦子沒問題吧
What the hell is wrong with you?
就在這裏
Right ... there.
槍法不錯啊
Nice shot.
你懷疑過我的實力麼 哈哈
Was it ever a doubt?
我承認 我剛才是有點懷疑的
Yes, I confess I had my doubts.
我可不允許你說我朋友吉本斯的壞話
That's for talking shit about my friend Gibbons.
項！跪在地上！
Xiang! Get on your knees! On your knees!
舉起手來！
Hands! Hands!
馬上跪在地上！
On your knees! Now!
來的正好啊
Just in time.
注意點 凱奇 小心他們誤傷你喲
Watch out. Cage. keep this up, people might mistake you for one of the good guys.
嘿 那個當官的
Hey, Suit.
你也拿到你想要的東西了
You got what you wanted.
我們也都知道 他不是個壞人
We both know that he is not the bad guy.
你知道 莫斯科爆炸事件的鍋該誰背麼
You know who would we blame for Moscow?
當然是讓這個活著的恐怖分子背咯 讓我們自己人背鍋多不合適
Better a living terrorist than a dead company man.
懂了我的意思麼
See what I'm saying?
走吧
Let's go.
把他帶回飛機 20分鐘後起飛
Back on the plane. I want wheels up in twenty.
夥計們 走吧
Let's go boys.
我們拿到"潘多拉魔盒"了
We recover Pandora's Box.
他們會派一個小隊去接你們
They will send an extraction team to pick you guys up.
項在他們手上
But they are taking Xiang.
塞麗娜
And Serena ...
如果你聯繫不上我 記得按9號鍵
you don't hear from me, remember, dial 9.
極限特工間會相互照應的
X takes care of its own.
你是不是把盒子給那個當官的了？
You gave it back to Marke, didn't you?
這飛機不錯啊 這麼寬敞 肯定造價昂貴吧
nice place. spacious, expensive.
閉嘴吧你
Shut up.
謝謝長官
Thank you, sir.
是的 傷亡降至最低 極限特工
Yes, minimal casualties. Triple-X performed ...
表現十分出色 超出預期
beyond any reasonable measured expectation.
讓我猜猜看
Let me guess.
是不是總統邀請我去辦公室坐坐呢
That was my invitation to the Oval Office.
10分鐘前 極限特工項目已正式取消
10 minutes ago, the Triple-X program was officially shuttered.
所有特工記錄已被清除 你們現在是國家公敵了
All active agents should be erased from record, and considered enemies of the state.
我建議你們不要拿槍指著我
It is just never a good idea to point a gun on me.
國安局的接應分隊一般都是這麼全副武裝的？
NSA extraction teams normally armed like they invading Fallujah?
一般來說不會的 盯緊他們
No, generally not. Watch the boys.
媽的
Shit.
不會真是那樣吧 他們會朝我們開槍吧？
Oh, it's happening, isn't it? They're going to shoot at us, aren't they?
我們撤
- Let's go!
好戲開始嘍
It's showtime.
看起來我們又要並肩作戰了
I guess we are on the same team now.
給我把槍
Give me one.
你懂我的 搞定他們不是問題
You know me. Wind me up, pointing the right direction.
走吧！
Let's go!
媽的這是要玩真的啊！
That shit is getting real! Does this happen when shit goes real?
我們要怎麼辦
What do we do?
準備開槍自衛吧
Just with bullets on.
遺憾的是 恐怖分子最後一次激活了潘多拉魔盒
Sadly, the terriost activated Pandora's Box ...
我們無法阻止他了
one last time before we could stop him.
你和你的小隊在爆炸中全數犧牲 盒子也被摧毀了
you and your entire team lost in the blast along with the device itself.
如果全世界都以為潘多拉魔盒已經徹底毀了
If the world thinks Pandora's Box has gone
他們就不知道我們還能用它監視他們
then they won't know we are using it to spy on them.
你只不過是一個暴君罷了
You're just another tyrant.
不 我是一個愛國者
No. patriot.
讓我來告訴你二者的區別是什麼
Let me educate you on the difference.
桑德！
Xander!
桑德 他們說這是你最後一次極限挑戰了 記得給我寄明信片喲
They say it is the last great adventure, cage. Be sure send me a postcard.
- 準備起飛！ - 出發吧
- engines hot! - Oh right let's go!
桑德！
Xander!
桑德·凱奇！
Xander Cage!
- 快跑！ - 大家分散躲好！
- Go, go! - Everybody spread out!
大家躲好！
Take cover! Move!
There, take cover!
真刺激啊
What a rush.
還好有貝奇給我的防彈護甲
Damn, Becky, that's a body armor.
嘿 我跟你說你真是不知羞恥
Hey, I told you that you got no manners.
你媽媽沒教過你穿褲子要拉拉鏈麼
Did your mother ever teach you how to zip up your pants?
不錯啊
Well
塞麗娜
Serena.
我這邊現在有點忙
We're a bit busy now!
潘多拉魔盒在那個當官的手上 她應該會讓一顆衛星墜毀在你們那裏
Marke has got Pandora's Box. She is gonna drop a satellite on top of you.
她要讓一個衛星墜毀在我們這邊
She is going to drop a satellite on us!
我可以暫時干擾一下信號
Not if I jam the signal!
給我找個電源
I need a power source!
去啊！
Go!
去那邊？就我一個人？
Over there? By myself?
去啊！
Go!
掩護我！
Cover me!
快點！去那邊！
Hurry up! Over there!
我解決下面的
I'll go low.
那上面的交給我
I'll go high.
我們去找那個特種大兵算算賬吧
See if we can find G.I. Joe.
你那邊受到信號干擾了麼
Are you getting signal interference?
媽的
Shit.
看樣子你也要把槍防身啊
Everyone needs back up, right?
說的對
Yeah, I guess.
來打一架啊
Let's do this.
尼克斯！
Nicks!
- 我有個想法了 - 別亂來！
- I got a plan. - No!
別亂來！
No!
聽我說 從現在開始聽我的 我告訴你要怎麼做 你再行動
Listen, from now on, I make the plans, you act ***!
媽的
Oh shit.
我的天 這真是他媽的太刺激了
Oh my god, this is fucking awesome!
混蛋 你腦子有坑吧 你就不該回來的
What's wrong asshole? Why do you come back?
不不 我終於想通了那個數學問題
No, I just finally figure out that maths problem.
想把你丟出去可真是費力啊
It's gonna take two flushes.
媽的 他們人數太多了 我們要撤出去
Oh shit, way too many. Let's get out of here.
快 撤到這邊
Get back
媽的
Oh shit
我不想死
I don't want to die
沖沖沖
Forward, push!
子彈都打完了 只能玩刀子了
This is all we've got.
我子彈用完了 你們還有麼
I am out of bullets! You got any?
沒了
No, nothing.
我也沒子彈了
I am empty!
數到三一起沖
We go on three.
咋沒人說話呢
What's up?
我的火箭筒不給力麼
Rock, paper, scissors ... grenade launcher.
德瑞斯·斯通
Darius Stone.
德瑞斯·斯通 2005年加入極限特工項目
DARIUS STONE XXX SINCE 2005
前海豹部隊特種兵
Former US Navy SEAL OFFICER
等了11年 終於有人按下9號鍵
Spent last 11 YEARS WAITING FOR SOMEONE to Dial 9
他2005年加入極限特工項目的
Triple-X since 2005.
感謝出手相助！
Thanks for the assist!
極限特工會相互照應的
X takes care of its own.
這簡直就是逗我啊
You got to be kidding.
選擇衛星
SELECT SATELLITE
我們失敗了
We failed.
桑德 馬克激活了"潘多拉魔盒" 有一個衛星正在墜向我們這邊
Xander, Marke activated the satellite and it headed towards us.
看起來我要玩一把自殺性撞擊了
I'm gonna have to take it to kamikaze style.
別 那無異於自殺 你可能沒法倖存的
Do not do it. It is suicide. Nobody could survive that fall.
叫尼克斯準備好錄像吧
Tell Nicks have that camera ready.
低空無傘自由落體 還有一個大煙花呢
Low alto free fall, no chute and a big fireworks
他們說這是我最後的冒險了
They say it is the last great adventure.
記得寄明信片哦
Make sure send a postcard.
為極限運動而生
I live for this shit
媽的
Shit.
尼克斯！
Nicks!
你把全程錄下來了沒
I hope you got that on camera.
沒有錄像的話沒人會相信的
If it ain't no video, it did not happen!
放心好啦 我全錄下來了 兄弟
Oh, yeah. Hall of Fame right here, bro.
- 我跟你說 這種雜技我也玩得來 - 你就使勁吹吧
- You know, I could have done that, right? - Bullshit.
馬克怎麼樣了
What happened to Marke?
自由落體 摔死嘍
The ground broke her fall.
你還是不相信好人嘛？
Still you do not believe in good guys?
有時候有點壞還是不錯的
It is okay to feel a little bad.
那是多壞呢
How bad?
我覺得吧 兄弟
Now, that right there...
你這個進場儀式可真是不錯啊
that was a hell of an entrance
你的車也不錯嘛
That's a hell of car.
吉本斯叫我好好保管這輛車
Gibbons told me to keep an eye on it.
他說等我用上它的那天 我就會明白為什麼要保管好它了
He said I would know why when I need to know why.
現在我明白了
now I know why.
車保存的很好啊 和我當時離開的時候一模一樣
It is exactly the way I left it.
我就開出去約會了一兩次
took it on a date or two
極限特工間相互照應嘛 哈哈
X takes care of its own.
所以我知道你會來幫我們的
That's why I figured you'll come through.
當然 畢竟能有幸同傳奇的桑德·凱奇並肩作戰
To get a chance to work with the legendary Xander Cage?
你要不要來給我簽個名呢
Where do I sign up?
你應該知道 你這次可是惹了一大幫人
You know you pissed a wrong damn picnic
全世界都會來追捕我們的
The whole world will be looking for us
我也無路可選了
I wouldn't have any other way.
你以為就你一個人知道怎麼裝死？
Think you are the only one knows how to play dead?
可算是找到你了
Gotcha.
能親自參加自己的葬禮 可真是離奇啊
It's pretty surreal to be on my own funeral.
"我覺得"
And I think to myself:
"世界真美好"
What a wonderful World
這首歌真不錯
I love that song.
如果壞人不再作惡
And it could be a wonderful world ...
這個世界的確挺美好的
if we stop doing bad shit to it.
如果你想讓我重出江湖 你就直接說一聲吧 何必這麼大費周章
If you wanted me out of retirement, you could have just asked, man.
不給你一點動力你哪會出山呢
You've always responded to less subtle motivation.
是麼？
now what?
你就先當個全民公敵 雖然世界暫時不知道你所存在的價值 但總有一天他們會明白的
You keep being a rebel the world doesn't know it needs.
你可以監督高官 消滅內部敵人
Watches the watchers, fight the enemy within.
媽的 那可真是複雜啊
Damn, that's so complicated.
真的麼
Really?
其實也沒那麼複雜 我這麼說吧
Let me simplify for you.
殺壞蛋
kick some ass
泡美女
Get the girl.
泡妞時記得耍帥就行了
And try to look dope while you are doing it.
你最擅長這些吧？
You can do dope, can't you?
我懂你的
Sure you can.
走吧
Junior, let's go!
有緣再見 桑德
I will see you there, X.
說的對 這些我都玩得來
I can definitely make that work.
字幕翻譯: william2568